Greek Chicken Meatballs. 35 min · 4 servings · Greek
Ingredients: 27. 1 cup mayo (Primal Kitchen or similar); 1 cup cucumber, diced; 1 tablespoon fresh lemon juice; 1 tablespoon garlic, minced
Section: Tzatziki Sauce
Step 1. Combine ingredients in a small food processor.
Step 2. Pulse to combine until smooth.
Step 3. Taste and adjust seasoning, as desired.
Step 4. Place in the refrigerator.
Section: Salad
Step 5. Combine tomatoes, cucumber, olives, and red onion in a medium mixing bowl.
Step 6. Add salt and Greek vinaigrette. Stir to combine and set aside.
Section: Greek Chicken Meatballs
Step 7. Combine ground chicken, egg, almond flour, salt, oregano, basil, dill, onion powder, garlic powder, pepper, mint, and feta cheese in a medium mixing …
Step 8. Use a cookie dough scoop to scoop out about 1 1/2 tablespoons of mixture, form a ball, and place on a large plate. Continue until all of the mixture …
Step 9. Bring a large/medium cast iron skillet to medium-high heat. Add a tablespoon of oil and spread evenly to coat the pan. Add chicken meatballs and sear…
You're ready. Use Make It for checkboxes on the page.